Good evening everyone, if you take a
complete analysis in our channel,
then under complete analysis
we
discuss in daily time frame, weekly time frame and monthly time frame,
green horizontal line indicates support
and red horizontal line
indicates resistance, so the stock selected for today is
ICICI
Prudential Life Insurance Company
Limited,
so let's start, those who have
not yet subscribed to this channel,
we request them to please subscribe to the channel,
if we look at the pattern it has created, what I can see is that it should
move positively, it went
above the moving average and
took a reverse from there, which means it is trying to go
up, so what should be the stop loss,
445 with a stoppage of 45 because
you will enter in it with that and or
if you want to enter now then the stop loss should be
445 or if you want to buy then
above 480, if we buy then your stop loss will be  It will be
460 and after that the
first target will be 500 and
50025 and then 540.
Its parallel stocks have also
seen a good rally, be it
HDFC Life Insurance or SBI
Life Insurance, there has been
a good rally in the sector or the value bank is coming from
Pan.
If we look at the weekly time frame, then
its low of 429 has
not been broken and it has started
moving upwards by taking support somewhere around 438
and this support has support here in the previous as well.
It is currently standing in multiple support zones, so it should take
support here and
above 480, a huge rally will be seen in it
like Delhi 420, I had also discussed
on the chart of the time frame, so 480 stop 440
of 440 case stop
W will
increase a lot, 425 425 625 650 will be
seen in the ministerial time frame, so for the last 3
months, it has been
trying to take this support in a concentration like  The
stop loss will be at 440. There has been
support around this before also
and if we look at this first then
it has been resistance so the resistance which was there
later becomes a support, it is
taking its third attempt where the support will
go above the moving average, it is
visible in the form of a script, so you
people are
requested that if you like this video then
like, share and comment on it and
definitely subscribe to the channel, that's all
for today, if anyone wants to
ask about any other script then
he can put it in the comment box, thank
you.